export const data = [
  {
    question: "Which device is required for the Internet connection?",
    option1: "Modem",
    option2: "Router",
    option3: "LAN Cable",
    option4: "Pen Drive",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the father of C language?",
    option1: "Steve Jobs",
    option2: "James Gosling",
    option3: "Dennis Ritchie",
    option4: "Rasmus Lerdorf",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which keyword is used to prevent any changes in the variable within a C program?",
    option1: "immutable",
    option2: "mutable",
    option3: "const",
    option4: "volatile",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: " Where in C the order of precedence of operators do not exist?",
    option1: "Within conditional statements, if, else",
    option2: "Within while, do-while",
    option3: "Within a macro definition",
    option4: "None of the mentioned",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "What is an example of iteration in C?",
    option1: "for",
    option2: "while",
    option3: "do-while",
    option4: "all of the mentioned",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is true for variable names in C?",
    option1: "They can contain alphanumeric characters ",
    option2: "It is not an error to declare a variable to",
    option3: "Variable names cannot start with",
    option4: "Variable can be of any length",
    ans: 3,
  },

  {
    question: "Which continent has the highest number of countries?",
    option1: "Asia",
    option2: "Europe",
    option3: "North America",
    option4: "Africa",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Junk e-mail is also called?",
    option1: "Spam",
    option2: "Fake",
    option3: "Archived",
    option4: "Bin",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "A computer cannot BOOT if it does not have the?",
    option1: "Application Software",
    option2: "Internet",
    option3: "Operating System",
    option4: "Mouse",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "First page of Website is termed as?",
    option1: "Index Page",
    option2: "Homepage",
    option3: "Sitemap",
    option4: "Pen Drive",
    ans: 2,
  },
];
